I lifted a huge Soy Latte with a big bang.
And now my arm muscles are cramping up.
It's a little twitchy.
I felt it when I used chopsticks for lunch.
I thought it was already here.
That was pretty hard on my muscles.
It's already in my soya muscles.
Soyer muscles.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, it's coming, isn't it?
Well, well...
Can I help you?
Oh, my God.
You usually dance so much.
But today we're doing a lot of poses.
I have to do a lot of poses.
I've been doing a lot of poses.
I didn't dance at all, so I didn't think it was hard at all.
I don't think it's hard at all, I'm having fun.
Yes, it's fun to make poses.
It's fun!
I wanted to show you my soirée.
These socks...
Not those... these... these... these Kraft Boss socks.
The person in charge of making sure the labels are facing the right way...
He turned it around a bit to kick Hunt's ass.
That's for sure.
That's an environment that doesn't usually exist.
That's an environment you don't usually have.
It's difficult because of the movement.
That's right.
If I'm even a little off when I'm posing...
If you can't see the latte's hand...
I was doing my best to say "soirasoi irasoi latte".
I was doing my best to say "so irasso irassoi latte".
You know, this "so-ay-ay-ay" feeling.
That's right, that's right.
The "Soyo" feeling.
Souyaa-ness and these socks.
Cooperation.
Yes.
So, instead of posing like this...
Don't just do it like that.
You know, show your feet... and stand there.
Craft Boss
You're particular about your footsteps, aren't you, Kyoua?
Right?
Did you have a hundred percent of the work?
A hundred percent?
You're the one with your feet on the ground, right, Faith?
I was almost always being carried.
I don't know... I guess it's a little bit like being on your feet or being on your feet.
Maybe this is the in-between part.
That's right.
Because the balance of the hair volume is not half as much as it should be.
It's more hairy.
In terms of formation.
If you're in front of someone with a lot of hair, there's a lot of pressure.
I'm putting him in the back rather than the craft boss.
Suzuka's legs have this sharpness or
It's very stable.
How do you like it?
It's like yoga.
It's a yoga feeling.
It's coming from here.
Tendons of energy
It's coming from here
I've got the longest legs.
It's been a bit of a morning
I've been a little too rough at the show.
I'm wearing concealer.
There you go.
Hey, guys.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Here it is.
It's a little bit like this.
Okay, now I'm going to have to get fired up.
What should I use as an engine? What should we use as an engine?
Let's make a scene one more time and let's all go!
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
that's when we get into the swing of things.
It's a time to get fired up.
When you need to get going
I use this to get pumped up.
It gets you going.
Now it's going up.
It's going to go up.
It's good when it gets hot.
I've got to stop it. I've got to stop it.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
We have to stop it. It's dangerous.
That's what I'm talking about. No heads.
We all start at once.
But maybe
Someone is faster by about 0.5 seconds.
But they're not aware of who started it.
It's like it's contagious.
If someone starts it...
If someone says it, you have to do it.
Let's go!
I don't know how I just did that.
That's what happens, doesn't it?
I'm really just a womanizer now.
A woman rider? I'm just a woman rider, but a woman rider.
Do you have any items for yourself?
Yes, I do.
I eat seasonal vegetables.
It's great!
I thought it was very kind of you to take care of yourself.
The other day, in between festivals, I got a lot of vegetables from my parents.
I received a lot of vegetables from my parents' house.
I made all kinds of summer food with those vegetables.
And when I ate them, I felt so much energy in my body.
I thought to myself, "This is what self-love is all about!
The soy latte I made this time is also a delicious kind of self-love.
And the seasonal food is also very delicious.
What is self-love? To heal yourself.
To heal. Love.
Yes, love yourself.
To love yourself. To take care of yourself.
To take care of yourself. We're gonna play a game.
Love yourself games. Love yourself games.
Love yourself game Love yourself game
Love yourself cartoons and love yourself cartoons and love yourself cartoons and love yourself cartoons and love yourself cartoons
Love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself, love yourself
Something like...
I don't know how to say it.
I'm crazy about it.
And once you lose yourself
away from my life
I think it's a great way to reset yourself.
It's a great reset
inside yourself.
I think it does for me.
I like to listen to music that I want to listen to at that time.
And the music that matches the music at the time.
and incense that matches the music at the time.
And it's amazing.
Through my ears and nose
So many parts of you can go to the dream world.
From the nose to the dream world.
By incense.
Oh, I see.
Stimulate the ears and nose.
It's like going into space.
It's time to take care of yourself.
I love coffee.
I can't drink coffee straight.
But I love coffee mixed with milk, like a latte.
I love coffee mixed with milk.
I'm very happy to have coffee at least twice a day, so I'm very happy to have coffee time.
I'm the kind of person who stops rehearsing and goes out to buy coffee.
I'm the kind of person who stops rehearsals to buy coffee.
I eat coffee at 5 o'clock.
Does it refresh you?
It's a nice change of pace.
Sometimes it makes me feel light-headed.
Sometimes it makes me feel relaxed.
I choose the strength and the type of coffee I drink.
What about snacks?
Snacks.
Eat snacks, sleep well, that's important.
But...
I can't say that the four of us on stage together at a summer festival is really the source of my energy.
I'd say that's really the source of our energy.
It's good to get some sun, isn't it?
The sun is important.
I get a lot of energy from the sun.
You've been spending a lot of time in the sun, haven't you?
That's right.
And with the clients too.
I've been spending a lot of time in the sun and getting a lot of energy from it.
I've spent a lot of time in the sun with the audience.
Standing on the stage with the sun and summer...
Yes.
That's how it is.
That's great.
When I'm cooking, I'm good at turning things inside out.
Rice...
That's right... that's right...
When you make fried rice crispy,
You know how fried rice becomes like this?
At that time, I always say, "That's right! I always say that.
I see.
That's true.
That's right. That's right. Sometimes it's like, "Oh, no, no!
I'm kind of doing the same thing.
Sure, sure, sure.
Isn't that it? The moment you wake up in the morning.
Isn't it good?
Oh, no! It's the moment you wake up in the morning.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to go to the bathroom...
Mom, you're too slow...
Instead of "good morning"...
All of them are probably just the start of another day.
When you start with that...
You'll feel the power in your belly, the energy, the rush...
It's like a breath of fresh air.
You should try it.
If you don't put a lot of energy into it...
If you don't put in the effort, it'll all rip.
Soyer.
It'll take your breath away.
Let's do it like this.
You have to put your foot down.
That's right.
It'll give you energy in the morning.
Yes, it does.
It seems to energize you in the morning.
Where's that Mr. Sakamoto? Well...
He doesn't look like he'd be too close.
I don't.
It's just...
Isn't it wonderful that you lift up Suzuka?
I'm the type of person who doesn't usually do it.
But when I lift up Suzuka
I lift it up as if I'm saying, "Oh, yeah!
I do it all the time.
I lifted up Suzuka today, too.
She's a really wonderful sailor.
I'm always so grateful
It's raining!
Sawyer
I'm also living a life that I don't usually
I'm not usually the kind of person who sows, but...
I wonder... the moment I rent a house, isn't it a lie, a lie to live that life? Come on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on, go on.
Go ahead, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead!
To the hairdressers and assistants around me.
Not so good, that's not so good.
Not so good.
Not so good
Not so good Come on, go, go, go, go, go, go!
To the hairdressers around you, to the assistants.
Not so good Soria
Soria, when she's a renter...
I'll go as far as I can.
We have to be very careful.
Soria, Soria, Soria.
But it's not dyed or anything.
Interesting.
That's funny.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen of the Grand Ole Opry, for your individuality and freedom.
I'm going to go out on a limb.
The leaders of our new school.
SOYA
Ladies and gentlemen
Take care of yourself with SOYLATTE!
It is important to love yourself very much!
Take good care of yourself and live every day with happiness!
That's all for the new school leaders!
Thank you